export const questions = [
    {
        question: "Who is the winner of champions league in 2008/09?",
        options: ["Realmadrid", "Chelsea" , "Manchester United", "Barcelona"],
        answer: "Manchester United"
    },
    {
        question: "Which player was arsenal capitain after cesc fabregas left in 2011?",
        options: ["Mikel Arteta","Vanpersie","Thomas Rosciky", "Jack Wilshire"],
        answer: "Vanpersie"

    },
    {
        question: "Which Liverpool manager led the team to their first premier league title in 30 years in 2020?",
        options: ["Arneslot","Jurggen Klopp", "Rafa Beneatez", "Jose Mouriniho"],
        answer: "Jurggen Klopp"
    },
    {
        question: "Which arsenal player scored the famous last-minute winner at Anfield in 1989 to win the title?",
        options: ["T.Henry", "Daglish","Michael Thomas","Tony Adams"],
        answer: "Michael Thomas"
    },
    {
        question:"Which player holds the record for most goals in a single La Liga season?",
        options: ["Ronaldinhio.Gocho","Lionel Messi","Cristiano Ronaldo", "D.Maradona"],
        answer:"Lionel Messi"
    },
        {
        question: "Who scored the winning penalty for Manchester United in the 2008 Champions League final?",
        options: ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Ryan Giggs", "Anderson", "Edwin van der Sar"],
        answer: "Anderson"
    },
    {
        question: "Which Arsenal manager led the club to an unbeaten Premier League season?",
        options: ["Arsene Wenger", "Unai Emery", "George Graham", "Mikel Arteta"],
        answer: "Arsene Wenger"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Manchester United's all-time top scorer?",
        options: ["Wayne Rooney", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Eric Cantona", "Ruud van Nistelrooy"],
        answer: "Wayne Rooney"
    },
    {
        question: "Cristiano Ronaldo scored his first Premier League hat-trick against which team?",
        options: ["Arsenal", "Newcastle United", "Chelsea", "Liverpool"],
        answer: "Newcastle United"
    },
       {
        question: "Which Manchester United manager won the treble in 1999?",
        options: ["Jose Mourinho", "Sir Alex Ferguson", "David Moyes", "Louis van Gaal"],
        answer: "Sir Alex Ferguson"
    }
  
]